The Hands of Orlac .
Beloved , in one day and one night I will again be with you .
I will hold you in my arms ... My hands will run over your hair ...
And I will feel your body tremble under my hands .
Orlac 's Concert .
Madam , it is 9 o 'clock and the train arrives at 11 .
To Montgeron !
He is alive !
It is 6 : 30 , Professor . Vasseur will be executed at 6 o 'clock ,
and 8 minutes later the car will bring the body to the clinic .
A train accident ... Mr. Orlac is severely injured .
And yet there is hope .
There is damage at the base of the skull , where we will operate ... Only ... "
Only his hands .
The hands ... Oh holy god ... The hands !
Save his hands ... His hands are his life ...
Save his hands ! His hands are more important than his life .
Save his hands .
After only a short time , you can come home ...
And sun , light and many flowers will greet you , when you come .
We will remove your bandages a little at a time .
Today you will see your face again .
Your eyes ... How I love you ... Your hair ...
And your hands ... Your beautiful , dear hands ...
There ... His head ... Doesn 't he see my hands ?
Is he laughing ?
Now ... He is so strong !
Tell me , what is under these bandages ? What secret do they hide ?
Well , then , in god 's name , we will reveal the secret .
Can these hands ever play again ?
The spirit rules the hands ...
Nature and a strong will can do anything .
Tomorrow ... Back tomorrow !
Here I will wait ... His first kiss and the first stroke of his hands .
The last night .
Your hands were not saved - Dr. Serral gave you different ones -
the hands of the executed murderer Vasseur .
Is it true ? Do I have the hands of the murderer Vasseur ?
How much longer ?
These hands will never strike a man again !
In half an hour ... No , only 30 minutes ...
I love you ... I love you ...
Do you have the paper from January 15th ?
The murderer Vasseur before his judges ...
Vasseur denied the act ...
But the fingerprints that were found gave the real evidence .
The dagger , which was stuck into the heart of the old racketeer ,
bore the same x mark on the handle .
Also , the dagger bore Vasseur 's unmistakable fingerprints .
The evidence was so clear that he received the death penalty .
I feel it also go out ... The arms spread ...
Until then , in the soul ... Cold , terrible , grim .
Twisted , twisted hands !
I don 't want to save you ? I will not come ... Not my ... No more ...
I cannot any more ... You are coming to kill ...
But I will not follow your terrible orders any more ... No more !
Don 't come any closer to me !
Go away ... I will not listen to you any longer !
Debauch your hands !
Don 't mix ... Away with your hands ... Those murderer 's hands !
Take away your hands . I don 't want these terrible hands .
Creditors .
Only wait a short time ... One month ...
I know it ... You demand blood ... Crimes ... Murder ...
Only one week !
Men don 't just control the hands ...
The head , the heart control the body ... Also the hands .
Until tomorrow !
My hat and my coat ...
l am going to my husband 's father . He is rich ...
He can help ... If he will ...
Don 't go there ... He is an evil man ...
He hates all men and even more so your husband ...
I can 't leave anyone to him ... At the least everyone from ... There .
Mr. Orlac , Paul can no longer play .
So we are in need . But Paul doesn 't know ... Help us !
He is your son ... Your flesh and blood ... Will you let us be ground in to the earth ?
Yes , I would like that ! I hate him !
Mr. 0rlac must himself go to see his father ... Today !
How will madam pay ?
Beloved , in one day and one night I will again be with you .
I will hold you in my arms ... My hands will run over your hair ...
That was ... Once ... My handwriting .
After one day and one night .
Go to your father ... Today ... He must help us ... We can 't go on ...
He refused to help ... And I have begged him so .
He is not a good man , your father ... He is evil . I fear him .
Murder !
The murderer Vasseur 's dagger !
The fingerprints of the criminal Vasseur !
Your sister is very ill ... Come right away ,
if you want to see her while she is still alive ... Come today !
Vasseur 's handwriting !
I do not know what secret he is going to give us ...
Vasseur has been dead for years , but his hands still live !
Paul Orlac , you are your father 's heir .
You will bring me a million tomorrow . At this time !
Money ? Money ? And that 's why you follow me awake and in my dreams ?
Why ?
For my hands !
Who are you ?
I am Vasseur , who was executed on July 13th .
The experiment that Professor Serral performed with your hands ...
His assistant made off with my head .
If I don 't get the million tomorrow at this time
I will go to the state prosecutor and tell him who your father 's murderer is .
Who is the murderer ?
You are ... Paul Orlac !
These fingerprints , which are clearly visible are the fingerprints of Vasseur .
And who has those fingers now ? You , Paul Orlac !
The letter , which passed through all the servants in the house ,
was written by the hand of Vasseur ,
and this hand is now your hand !
The dagger , with which the murder was committed , is Vasseur 's dagger with the x ' .
Your maid will swear that she saw you with it ... In your hand !
Perhaps you did not commit the murder , but you cannot prove it .
What is happening to me ? Am I crazy ?
Won 't you tell me what is bothering you ?
I have the feeling , that these hands are drawing me ... To crime ...
I must bring him the money .
You will tell the state prosecutor everything ...
Who will believe me ?
They will believe you as I believe you .
I go in a free man .
Wait , perhaps you have some news for the evening paper .
It is odd , but I don 't know whether I am experiencing reality or a dream .
A stranger ...
He was then executed ...
I have seen with my own eyes the work of the guillotine on a neck .
Mr. Orlac , we thank you for your evidence ...
Go this evening , bring the money with you to the stranger ,
and we will follow you .
Someone well known to us ... Mr. Nera , at last . Assistant to Dr. Serral , â  
one of the least talented crooks in the world .
I am also a blackmailer ! But ... You are searching for the murderer ?
Haven 't you considered that the murderer has Vasseur 's hands ...
I don 't have those hands .
I can tell you who has those hands .
Mr. Orlac , I arrest you !
Mr. Orlac is innocent . Nera is the murderer !
Be quiet !
Tell me ! What about the fingerprints of the executed Vasseur ?
Nera was Vasseur 's friend ... He secretly made imprints of Vasseur 's fingerprints .
And then he had rubber gloves made ... With Vasseur 's fingerprints .
And so he killed the elder Orlac ...
And so he killed the old racketeer ,
and then made it look as if Vasseur had done it ...
Vasseur died an innocent man .
If Vasseur was not guilty , then my hands are pure ...